[
  {
    "question": "How Long Ago Was The Earth Formed?",
    "a1": "About 3.7 Million Years Ago",
    "a2": "About 823 Billion Years Ago",
    "a3": "About 650,000 Years Ago",
    "a4": "About 4.6 Billion Years Ago",
    "right": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Large Is Jupiter Compared To Earth By Volume?",
    "a1": "2,400 Times",
    "a2": "100 Times",
    "a3": "1,300 Times",
    "a4": "750 Times",
    "right": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Many Planets Are Between Earth And The Sun?",
    "a1": "Two",
    "a2": "Three",
    "a3": "Eight",
    "a4": "One",
    "right": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Of Earth's Surface Is Covered By Water?",
    "a1": "About 55%",
    "a2": "About 70%",
    "a3": "About 24%",
    "a4": "About 82%",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Earthly Feature Is Responsible For The Magnetic Field That Surrounds The Planet?",
    "a1": "The World's Oceans",
    "a2": "Volcanic Eruptions",
    "a3": "The Molten Core",
    "a4": "Gravitational Pull From The Sun",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is Earth's Average Distance To The Sun?",
    "a1": "92,956,050 Miles",
    "a2": "83,041,430 Miles",
    "a3": "405,321,783 Miles",
    "a4": "1 Light Year",
    "right": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Shape Does The Earth Take?",
    "a1": "A Square",
    "a2": "A Circle",
    "a3": "A Sphere",
    "a4": "A Triangle",
    "right": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Many Days Does It Earth Take To Orbit The Sun?",
    "a1": "1",
    "a2": "31",
    "a3": "324",
    "a4": "365",
    "right": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Large Is Earth Compared To Other Planets In The Solar System?",
    "a1": "It Is The 4th Largest",
    "a2": "It Is The 5th Largest",
    "a3": "It Is The 7th Largest",
    "a4": "It Is The 2nd Largest",
    "right": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Most Abundant Element In The Rocks Of Earth's Crust?",
    "a1": "Silicon",
    "a2": "Sulfur",
    "a3": "Oxygen",
    "a4": "Calcium",
    "right": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is The Closest Planet To Earth?",
    "a1": "Pluto",
    "a2": "Mercury",
    "a3": "Venus",
    "a4": "Mars",
    "right": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Of Earth's Water Is 'Fresh'?",
    "a1": "About 3%",
    "a2": "About 17%",
    "a3": "About 23%",
    "a4": "About 44%",
    "right": "1"
  }
]
